The invocation will be by Fire Chief Robert Brighton.
Brighton, please.
Father, I thank you for this day, and I thank this community that we live in.
I ask if you've let citizens are right here tonight, and if people are right here tonight.
I ask if you've walked over this.
Thank you for sending these grudges to the name of Brighton.
Amanda.
Apply my leg to the light of the United States of America.
I'm sure you're in public for where it stands.
I'm nation.
Under the law.
Either it is.
Or for public input or unscheduled personal appearances.
I will have you in the next one.
Next week.
Okay.
Number five.
Consent agenda.
Staff recommends we approve out of six or three nine.
Take the motion to approve.
Back.
Ten.
Approver.
Then before.
If you want it delivered object.
That's your tech professional services.
I'll drop.
Studies for the g ra.
Licensing.
I don't know if the council has any questions on this.
modeling that it's being utilized in response to the GRDA study.
This ongoing duty study because you'll quickly get out of my realm of expertise.
Mr. Engineer.
But this is the ongoing study that GRDA has to do regarding the release of things.
And then as anyone affected upstream, we review that study.
So we need to do that.
We need to do that.
All right.
We'll have a discussion in possible action on.
random of winter storm cost recovery method. Looks like you.
Being that we are going to go with the route of paying our geared abil for the next
country over the next 12 months. So it gives the option of paying it all at one turn,
paying it out over 12 months or paying it over the next 10 years. So our choice was to pay
it out over the next 12 months. So they will send us a bill. We can pay it monthly or we can
pay it all in one month. So I'm not kind of tired. And it's allowed some time to kind of work
on, you know, we talked about industrial customers. We've been doing based on, or you should
that month. And this allows us to kind of help the right structure for the other customer classes
and go from there. I think the way to ask the last meeting is this, will this be a per meter,
and as of right now we will look at just doing like a KWAH charge. So it doesn't matter how many meters
you had, it would just be based on your usage. And the payback would be over three years. And we would
just have the performance. I think that's kind of what we've got that been, is setting the rate
structure for that. Once we paid it back, we would, you know, if we paid it back sooner than three years,
obviously any, we would shut it down then or we took, you know, 38, 39 months and we would keep doing it
to the end. Because the number of customers couldn't, you know, increase or decrease over the next three
we also talked about there being an extra line on them on the bill. That's a weird amount of
paying. That's not too much. We're going to go on that. Okay. And then as soon as we paid off that line,
we go away. And again, this, this is not the final decision on how we're going to recover. This simply
is the vote of the council, which would give us the authority to notify one, notify GRDA of the decision
of the city of whether or not we're going to use funds in which they go out and secure the loan for
all of their customers and which we would be responsible for interest or if we are going to be one of
their customers that will just simply pay them in full over 12 months at no interest. So this puts them
on notice of what our, what the council's position is in there. And then there will be continued conversations
as a council as we move forward making final determinations of how and how we're going to recover.
So this just lets us notify GRDA and pay that 2.7 million once they do it.
there's a look at her motion to breathe that.
Yes, sir.
I'm most make a motion that we have to fight them out over the next moment.
So before you vote, let me add one thing that we were discussing, Tyler and Bowen, I
were discussing.
We probably should do this, telling him that that's what we're wanting to do, but do
it under protest to reserve our rights that we have, we may have, we may not have, we're
not sure, but just to protect our rights should, for instance, through some litigation,
they recover the money in some other way.
Just as an example.
Anyway, we want to check into the rate civilization fine.
Right.
And Josh, what a good point.
The last meeting.
So thank you, Josh.
You mentioned, you know, that Northeast covered a lot of the Earth that we got to
check into, and the fears that they've either part of the came out and that came out,
but it's just a chunk of it, so a lot of Northeast do not, you know what I'm saying?
We don't know those exact numbers yet, but we kind of don't want to push back on the area, and
say, hey, it came out, we can do this, a lot of you doing this, I hope you're going to be able to
consider that.
I'll amend my motion to include man's safe sands and bucks.
Thank you.
All right.
Thanks, Tyler.
Well, the new business of any of those businesses, it's supposed to be this agenda.
13.
I mean, trust it.
Community announcements.
14.
Gender.